Hello Hello friends my name is Alok Sharma if you want to
see the bank then we are
not going to hurry here but we are going to
talk about an informative thing that
comes in the information that some time back
even I was not aware of that thing so when you do not know something then
you get very
worried
so we are going to talk on Aarushi topic what happened
in Chakli was that on
5th December 2019 I had purchased a bike in my name
Bajaj Pulsar 125
Times were running well and was fine what
happened one day it was 6th August
we were riding it in August once it met with an
accident then its front
headlamp and we went through the
screen in the voucher so at that time
someone told me that you can make a claim
which on making a claim all these things can be
replaced so the thing about typing knowledge is that
I do not know how to do it
and what is the procedure I
asked many people so many people told me in many
ways  He answered my question, so
I thought why don't we do it our way
and understand how a film is made,
Prithvi Amit, you can see I have this
car paper, I bought a Bajaj Pulsar on
5th December 2019, it had been 8-9 months since I was
working, then it met with an accident,
then this was my card, the car was in my name,
you can see the complete details of the
car are in my name, it happened
because after the accident, someone,
my friend, told me
that you can claim it, they will
put it to you in the claim, so I did
not know how much money it would cost, how it would be, I
asked many people,
but many people, I mean you can understand
and everyone has different answers, so
actually, at that time, while dealing with the bike,
I had told the bike agency that
I need Bajaj Allianz bike
insurance, thankfully they
provided it to me, Bajaj Allianz, they were
giving something else late at night, the company arrangement, that is, the
insurance company had told me  But you should keep in mind
that if they gave me my 6, I will
put the photo of the car at the time of the accident
here, there was a lot of
loot and Sangh
branches, I will put the photo of
my car here, so
I directly got the number of my Bajaj Alarms
insurance company from Google, if
you are an insurance
company, you can go there on Google and
type in the name of the company which comes,
like my name is Bajaj Reliance customer
care toll free number, from there you can
get the number of whichever company from Google,
you can call them, I called them and
told them all the information, then they
said that I have an app, you
can go to it and register for yourself, so they called Africa Europe Helper and
asked for it, the name of the app was Ustad Yaan,
so I went there and I did not understand anything, then
I called them again, the old man
and said that I am not able to understand, please get
my claim processed by your guru,
he said okay, he asked me in
whose name will you take the full details of the car accident,
who was driving the car and  One
important thing you have to keep in mind is
that whoever was driving the car that caused the
accident must have a driving license. If they do
n't have a driving license, the
claim won't be processed. You
can't file a claim. Actually, he wasn't driving.
My brother, Sadho Jhal, was driving the car.
He had a driving license. If
you don't have a driving license,
you can do this. If you have a
friend, you can use his driver's license. When they
ask for information about
who was driving, you can provide their name,
not yours. If you don't have a driving
license, I did the same. I was
not driving the car with my friend.
If you're in the same situation, I'm telling you
what you should do. I provided their
driver's license. They
ask for the driver's license number, the
name of the driver's license, and the full vehicle
details.
After that, they register your claim.
In my case, the
money was credited to my account. It took just three days for the claim to be processed. It took
one day. One day,
he appointed his senior, who is his employer, to
look at my car.  I started making a claim one day and
after a day I got a message on my
registered mobile number that Sir your
agent will go to your house, whichever
location you have given,
he will go there and verify the central address of your vehicle, okay,
use the name of the vehicle, when the message reached me or the
number of the senior employee who was going to the insurance company was also written on it, I called him and
said Sir you are coming to
see my vehicle, whatever I
mean I am coming to see the claim in it,
he said no
I will not come to see your vehicle, you take
1520 photos of the vehicle and
send them to me, okay, so I
took 1520 photos for him, whatever you have in MS Word,
I took a photo of it and
sent it on his WhatsApp,
after that he said that you get a beard
card, the card which
you just showed you in your mouth, Sushma, I
need a photo of that card as well, I need a photo
of the driving license as well and I need a
photo of the insurance as well, where
is this Tata Photos  So I sent it from mine,
he agreed to it, I
sent it to him, next day I had Rs. 3500
in my account, it got
transferred to my account and it got removed from there,
ok, Rs. 3500 got added to my account at a discount, so
this is the process, now
I will show you my car, you will
say friend, first you show me your car, so
I will show you my car, ok,
first I will show you mine and
I will also attach the photo of the damage and I got it
replaced, I will show you that as well,
friends, one more important thing
you should always keep in mind that
while making a claim for your car, you should never make a claim for your car
through the agency,
you should never make a claim from the agency from where you bought your car,
I am saying this
because they ask for money, it happened
in my condition that I went to the agency from where I bought my car
and I was asked to make a
claim for my car, then
they said that you will have to
deposit the money first, yes, they
said that whatever you have, it means its
interest  It has happened that this lesson will cost ₹4000 and
you will have to deposit 2000 rupees first
and later this money will be refunded to you,
I asked sir how much will be refunded,
he said that out of 4000, you will have to pay 3000 rupees for the
response over 1000 claim, so
friends I request you
never to get your car back claim done from an agency, it can cause
you a lot of
loss and in my situation
I did not have to pay a single rupee for the young man's car,
whatever
I got replaced, whatever damage was there,
whatever was the Krishna, the
insurance company gave me all the claims
on my account, I will not have to spend a single rupee from my side
and if you
get it done by the agency then it will take you time, they will take
your car, leave it here,
then your work will start at the fort, then they will
put it to you, you do not have to do this at all,
you have to claim on your own, whether you have to go
during pregnancy or somewhere,
only you, but if you do not know the number, then you
yourself  Get insurance done, this company has
that number there,
talk to the insurance company people
and the director will tell you his program,
he will tell you in two to three days, four days, you will get the
money in your account, you do
n't have to do much, just call him and
tell him everything that I have to do this, your
problem will be solved, just
keep this information in mind
because there can be a lot of problem on this,
thank you, so
friends, this is not my car, you
can see it, I placed this
digest, this is the relation of the press and here you
can see it, it is still visible here,
you had this, so I did not get it replaced, I can get it
wrapped up more, and
I will show you in the photo,
here this loan is cheap and here with this
I have replaced it and I did
not have to pay any money in it,
although I mean the insurance company itself
provided me the money,
Rs 3,751, whatever loss you incur, it will be
sent to your account, okay, so this is my
car,
now you can see it, Pulsar  It is 125, I used to use
it, 125 is my car now, it is
not complete, then it had run 4000 kms, so this is
my press, this was it, I will
show you in the photo, now I got it
replaced, it did not cost me any
money to get it replaced, the
insurance company itself
provided me the full amount, I did
not have to spend a single rupee on it, okay
friends, you can see,
I can call you myself to the insurance company
and get it done myself, then you do
not need to worry about it, they will themselves
give you the solution, they will provide you whatever information you want,
but
yes the important thing is that you will have to send them the correct
information and photo of your car in a
clear manner,
thank you friends, see you in the next video, till then
subscribe to my channel
and do not forget to like and comment on the video and
what information do you need, please do
mention it in the comment, thank you